<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on sahilmn</title>
    <link>https://altairmn.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on sahilmn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:46:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://altairmn.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Progressive GAN Implementation</title>
      <link>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2021/08/18/progressive-gan-implementation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2021/08/18/progressive-gan-implementation/</guid>
      <description>Progressive GAN Implementation Link (code): https://github.com/altairmn/progressive-gan
Paper: https://arxiv.org/abs/1710.10196
Overview Progressive GANs work by gradually adding layers to the discriminator and generator of the GAN during training. The benefits of this approach include faster training, reduced amortized memory and GPU usage over the course of training, and qualitatively better results. This paper is focused on training a GAN for generating from the distribution of CelebA-HQ dataset.
Notable Points  Loss function is the wasserstein loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICLR 2021 (Day 1)</title>
      <link>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2021/05/04/iclr-2021-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 02:06:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2021/05/04/iclr-2021-day-1/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m virtually attending ICLR 2021 so I can tip my toes back into ML. Here are a few papers I found interesting on my exploration on day 1 (some of them appear as posters or oral sessions on later days):
The Traveling Observer Model 🎠 Link
This approach enables multi-task learning by using the same model for all tasks.
🤩 Result On the UCI 121 dataset which has a set of 121 classification tasks, TOM performs very well compared to other approaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing StarGAN</title>
      <link>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2021/01/14/implementing-stargan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 23:03:33 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2021/01/14/implementing-stargan/</guid>
      <description>Implementing StarGAN Paper: StarGAN: Unified Generative Adversarial Networks for Multi-Domain Image-to-Image Translation
Introduction Image-to-image translation refers to mapping images between different domains. For example, changing the facial expression of a person from smiling to frowning, or changing the gender of a person from male to female, or their hair color from black to brown.
For each domain (ex: black_hair_color, or beard) every image has a value. In the dataset that we use, the values are yes/no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passage</title>
      <link>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2019/12/08/passage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 23:53:09 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://altairmn.github.io/post/2019/12/08/passage/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow will come today
You be ready with your suit and your jacket
Your smile, ready to crank it
For if you&amp;rsquo;re not prepared, it&amp;rsquo;ll pass
You by as surely as today has
And then again you will lament
the hands on the dial won&amp;rsquo;t ever relent
And as they pose when moon comes up
Your spirits drop, your breath lets up
&amp;ldquo;Oh why can&amp;rsquo;t I unravel in nature-like
No beginnings, no ends, just motion</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
